Hello everybody. Welcome to NFA live.
I'm joined as ever by my compatriots
Guy from Coin Bureau. Guy, how is the
market treating you today?
>> It's it's treated me worse, Rob. That's
as much as I can say really.
>> Yeah, that sounds reasonable. And Ben,
the most loved person on Twitter. Ben,
how you doing?
>> Pretty good. How about you?
>> Not too bad. Got a lot of things to talk
about. Let's jump into it. So first of
all, if you're not subscribed to these
two gentlemen there is a plethora of
different channels you can choose from
over at Coin Bureau. I won't go through
all 20. And then also Ben's got a great
channel over there. And doing a great
job on the thumbnails, my man. Great
job. These are way better than the
originals.
>> So
>> I mean, uh now that I've hired uh
ChatGPT, it makes my life easier.
>> So basically, Ben, you are you are
saying that AI is going to replace jobs.
I get it. That's okay.
>> No, see here's the thing, Rob. And I
want to be clear. Like people say I'm a
pessimist. I'm not. I'm an optimist.
I didn't have anyone creating thumbnails
before. So I created This is just a new
thing that AI is providing. It's not a
negative thing. It's just improving
something that didn't exist before.
>> That is true. I think uh
uh we all should take a look at the
silver lining. So speaking Speaking of
silver linings
let's talk about where the heck is the
bull run?
Now Jim Cramer is not wrong every single
time. Just a lot of the time. But
there's one thing that he did say that
did make a lot of sense. There's always
a bull market somewhere. You just have
to find it. So as we go through the
digital asset space and we see things
going down, well your side which we'll
get to in a bit, also midterm election
year which we're in right now where the
heck is the bull market? What are you
looking at right now and into the
future? Guy, I'd like to start with you
on this one
to tell us where to actually look. And
this could be anything outside of crypto
in crypto or outside of crypto.
>> Well, spoiler alert, Rob, and it is not
in crypto. Um
>> [laughter]
>> I don't think we're I'm not anticipating
a bull market there anytime soon. What's
What I think has been really interesting
over the last, you know, over the last
year or so particularly is just how fast
these bull markets move. I mean, do you
remember not so long ago
gold and silver were absolutely ripping.
>> That's right.
>> And gold now, I mean, I think gold has
fallen back to around 4K. I'm I'm not
sure what silver's at off the top of my
head.
But, you know, it's it's fascinating
because this is a dynamic that we've
observed in crypto quite a lot over the
last few years. You know, you get these
sort of localized little mini bull
markets if you like in specific sectors.
And as soon as they start, you know,
they seem to end. And that's that also
seems to be, you know, that's something
that I'm noticing in sort of traditional
markets as well.
Um however, having said that, I mean,
you know, look, for for for most of this
year we've been talking about the AI
trade, haven't we? These you know, the
hyperscalers
spending absolutely vast amounts of
money um on the AI buildout. And
obviously there's been a lot of
questions come with that, you know, are
we in a bubble? Is this sustainable? And
what have you? So, what's been really
interesting to see
recently is the fact that where has that
money been going? What have they
actually been spending it on? And the
answer it to you know, to some extent is
memory and chips.
And so, what we're seeing now is a
fascinating kind of move away, you know,
um
some of these big the likes of Nvidia
and Alphabet are both sort of down
recently.
Whilst on the other hand, we've got
things like Micron, the American the
US-based chipmaker and SanDisk, which
is, you know, all about memory. These
guys have been absolutely ripping. And
the reason for it is is that these guys
are downstream. You know, these guys are
receiving all this money that the
hyperscalers have been spending. And
yesterday we were talking about this to
some of our Discord subscribers.
Uh over the last few days.
You know, Micron Micron came out with
their earnings yesterday and they were
they were insane. They reported fiscal
third quarter revenue of $41.5
billion
and that was but $35.5 billion was the
expected number. So they exceeded
expectations
significantly. Earnings per share were
were $25
and $20.50 were expected. And what's
crazy is that they're talking about the
next quarter, they're forecasting $50
billion of revenue and $31
earnings per share.
So
you know, these guys and what was what
was also particularly interesting about
that call was that
they were talking about how the fact
that
at the moment these semi this this next
generation of cars, particularly EVs,
but you know, cars in general um which
obviously have more and more software
built into them. Micron is saying that
semi-autonomous cars use more than 5x
the memory and storage of an average
vehicle.
And humanoid robots could use roughly
10x the memory of these more advanced
cars. So
the the immediate
the immediate demand is coming from
hyperscalers, you know, data centers and
whatever. But it is quite easy to see a
sort of long-term thesis for the memory
and chip trade even without necessarily
even even if AI were to dramatically
slow down or decrease spending or
whatever, that would obviously hurt the
overall market and these these guys in
particular. But it's easy to see that
the demand for memory, the demand for
chips is probably only going to keep
climbing.
Um and so it was so that seems to be at
the moment where the current bull market
is. And the question is how long can
that be sustained for? And I guess if
the hyperscalers are forced to scale
back uh just how much they're spending,
then that could bring it all to a
juddering halt. Uh but there is I think
a very interesting long-term case for it
as well. And I kind of like it because
it's it's boring, isn't it? Memory and
uh chips, I mean yeah, that's real sort
of
it's it's not exactly going to set the
world on fire. But again, you know, I I
always I always feel kind of drawn to to
to sectors like that that are just, you
know, boring but fundamental. So, the
memory and chip trade is where is where
the bull market currently is. How long
it remains there is uh is another
question entirely.
>> Holy smokes. Well said. I did not know
about Micron. This is fantastic. SanDisk
looks pretty good. And of course, it's
one of those things where, oh, if I just
would have known about this earlier. So,
everybody, if you're not following Guy
over Quiver give that a follow, that's
for sure.
Ben,
what do we got? Where is our bull
market?
>> I mean, Guy's right. Uh
everything he said I think I agree with.
Um
you know, going into the summer, I I was
talking about we would likely see sort
of a small correction in June
uh in the stock market. And we've kind
of had that.
So, I I wouldn't be surprised if
equities, you know, just in general,
like the overall market, went back up. A
lot of times in midterm years, the stock
market will sort of get a correction in
June. Kind of a shallow correction, like
5 to 10%. Um
and then we'll rally again kind of into
August, September time frame before then
getting a larger drop at the end of the
midterm year. So, I guess that's where
you could say it is, like that.
International markets as well, like
international funds.
Um
and then I and then and then the
argument becomes once that gets a
correction
because I mean
we know where the bull market currently
is. I guess maybe another question is
like where is it going to be, you know?
Um right.
And so if we do get a correction in the
stock market in the back half of the
year um
then you might actually see the bull
market come back to Bitcoin.
But like you know, that's probably a few
months away. So that's what I'm sort of
planning for to see it rotate back over
to to the crypto verse, but probably not
until say closer to the fourth quarter
of the year. So that's my guess.
>> Sounds pretty good. I'll take that. It
sounds pretty reasonable going that way.
So that will take care of the first
question, which is interesting. It's
something definitely take a look at, but
the next part really comes down to
four-year cycles. Which I know some
people believe, some people don't
believe. It's pretty much is what it is,
but I got to tell you it comes back to
what Tony Robbins said. Take a listen. I
think this is about a couple seconds or
so. Let me see if you can hear this.
>> And there's three skills you want to
give your kids, and you want these three
skills if you want to succeed for the
rest of your life. First is you have to
be able to recognize patterns. It won't
matter what the jobs are, won't matter
what the business is.
If you can recognize patterns, you have
an edge.
Things look like
>> Yeah, sounds pretty reasonable. I think
if we can recognize these patterns, we
have an edge. And one of those patterns
was the four-year cycle. Now
unfortunately, some of those things
didn't really lived up to it. Trump. And
we can see that Bitcoin price has never
dropped below election day. That's not
true. That's actually has faltered. I
thought it was going to be the bottom of
69K and it wasn't. However, if we take a
look at time frames, all-time high to
all-time highs
1,477 days between 13 and 17, then 1,424
and 28. All-time low to all-time highs
essentially the same thing, 1,068 days.
All-time high to all-time low, again 400
365 days. So the question that I have
for both of you is as such.
The four-year cycles, has it surprised
you? It surprised me as how it's
actually kept going and actually has
come out to this point. But Ben, I'll
start uh I'll start with you on this
one. I think we're in alignment here.
Four year cycles, are you surprised it
actually has gone through and are there
any discrepancies that you've seen?
>> No, I mean it seems like so far it's
been the it's been the the one thing
that hasn't failed in terms of
predicting like what Bitcoin's going to
do. So,
uh I think we defer to the four year
cycle until it's proven until it proves
wrong.
Um I mean it just keeps on working out
and
it's one of those things like, you know,
fool me once
shame on you, fool me twice shame on me,
right? Like
the I I don't understand why people
fight it so much, you know, like it's
I know the uh the temptation to fight it
is always there because, you know, we
all want to find a reason for why it
can't be that simple, but it then just
continues to be that simple. So, until
until something different happens, I I
would say the four year cycle is is
probably one of the better indicators
that we have uh for navigating
Bitcoin. I mean all you If you think
about it,
there's like a thousand indicators, but
all you really ever had to do was buy
Bitcoin at the end of the midterm year
and sell it in the fourth quarter of the
post having year. And if you just did
that last three cycles, you would have
basically outperformed
just as good if not better than any
other indicator out there.
>> Yeah, I got to agree.
And then Guy, same thing with you. Four
year cycles, were you
or were you like, "Yeah, that's pretty
much par for the course."
>> Well, what is it they say? You know, the
the most fatal words are in investing of
this time is different.
>> True.
>> Um so, yeah, why
why should this time be any different, I
guess. Yeah, I mean I I like we say, it
it it it it plays out it works until
until it doesn't, but it's it's hard to
see why how it would necessarily change.
So, yeah, I wouldn't say I I wouldn't
say I'm surprised. I
should have paid more attention to it if
nothing else.
>> Yeah, that's for sure. We should have
all paid a little more attention to it.
It wasn't so much about the
the bottoms. It was about the tops. And
I think like Ben just just talked about,
we can have a thousand indicators and
guess what? All you got to do is just go
by the by the numbers for the four-year
cycle, it would have worked out. Now,
can it continue on that?
A lot of people will say, "No, you
can't. At some point it will drop off."
But I got to tell you as far as like
bottom indicators,
one of the things that kind of lines up
is the 200-day moving average or
200-week moving average, I'm sorry.
And we can see here that this is
actually dropped below.
Let me just scheme. So, the moving
average is 62 and today we are at Are we
still at 62? Or the Bitcoin price is
61,000? I'm not for sure.
But that's the 200, 250 drops us to
roughly
57k. And if we go to the the bottom of
the barrel, the 350 week, I mean you're
looking at
47k. So, I think anywhere between there
is pretty good. But as a reminder,
people say, "Well, that's kind of scary,
Rob." I don't think you should be
scared.
All you got to do is just take a look at
these cycles
and they're just have been lining up
pretty well.
This was the last
Actually, let me go back here. Here's
the tops. Here's the bottom.
Here's the top.
Here's the bottom.
Here's the tops again.
And then here's the bottom. Usually it's
about a year, but just stick around. I
think you'll like where we're going. Not
financial advice, that's where we're at.
So, that'll take care of that question.
Now, let's move into the last ones,
which is this.
There is a fundamental shift. We're at a
crossroads right now.
And people will say, "Well, it doesn't
really matter because, you know, there's
a bunch of liquidity out there. There's
a super cycle coming." This is the M2
money supply from 2018. Up into the
right, sounds pretty good. These are the
midterm years. These are the bad bear
years. Then we take a look at 2022
M2 money supply kept going down.
So, of course they can say that's the
reason for it. That's the reason for all
this different volatility and the bear
markets. But then take a look at the M2
money supply
for 2026
we're going up into the right.
And it still keeps coming.
So, for that and then also we've got an
issue with the Federal Reserve. Looks
like we got a split coming up on the
next uh
FOMC meeting at 29th July. Looks like a
60/40 or 65/34 split to actually raise
rates. And that's in July, September it
gets even more stringent.
And then on top of that, we've got the
socioeconomic problems or the
geopolitical issues with US and Iran.
And I don't know who is telling me the
truth. Seems like every single person is
lying on top of the fact we've got
stable coins at all-time highs according
to DeFi Lama. 314 billion is sitting on
the sidelines. And then we've also got
Warren Buffett and Berkshire Hathaway.
By the way, it says 347 billion here,
but I think it's almost 400 billion
they're just sitting on waiting to
deploy it. So, we have all these things
going on plus the fact that real
disposable income just turned negative
for the first time in at least the last
two and a half years.
So, that means we've got a lot of
a lot of bottlenecks coming in.
So, the question for you guys is this
and I guy I'd like to start with you on
this one.
Is it best just to sit it out? Just wait
where things go or do you have to deploy
right now because we're going down?
>> I think
I mean I the danger here is if is is in
waiting for something that that never
comes. You know, it it's well, I think
you only have to look at for instance
Berkshire Hathaway. I mean they those
guys are sitting on an absolute mountain
of cash, aren't they? And you're like,
well uh
Buffett and Co. they must know what
they're doing.
They must see you know a crash of
you know a decline on the horizon. And
then you look at the AI trade like we
were talking about earlier and you think
well that's you know that that can't
last.
And it's all fair enough and it's
it is there's there's definitely
something to be said about having about
holding cash. I think cash should always
be
a significant if not you know not
necessarily a majority but certainly a
significant chunk of your overall
portfolio should be cash to deploy at
times like that. But I think if you're I
think if you're waiting solely in cash,
if you're if you're just not investing
at all
I think that's a recipe for for disaster
really because
you know going back to what you were
saying about the M2 money supply
constantly going up. I mean there you
are like you know inflation is is is a
constant thing. It may slow down, it may
speed up but we know that that the value
of fiat currencies is eroding every
single day which is why you know we have
things like Bitcoin. But I think if you
are if you're just sitting solely in
cash waiting for the big crash, waiting
for it all to
all to come crumbling down and for you
to get a generational entry point into
whatever asset it is you're you're
watching
I think that there is a real risk there
that you end up waiting so long that
that inflation has has eaten away at any
you know at at so many potential gains.
So I think you know you need to hold
assets to offset inflation. And I think
as any investor as any seasoned investor
will tell you you need to keep your time
horizon long. You need to trust that
markets will go up in the long term
because if we look you know again going
back to that chart you were showing of
of Bitcoin. I mean that is what it's
done. Okay, there have been some there
have been some dips along the way
but essentially like the M2 money supply
it is up and to the right and and the
chart of the S&P and the chart of gold
and whatever else will will will tell a
similar story. So, if you're not Okay,
it it reminds me of I think it's the
Chinese proverb that says the best time
to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The
second best time to plant a tree is now.
Um
and look, you know, without if you're
not willing to take on risk even at a
time when you think, "Wow, this market
is looking pretty frothy. These asset
prices are really inflated."
If you're not willing to take on risk,
then you won't get the reward.
Uh and short-term price action really is
is just noise at the end of the day. If
you have a long enough time horizon, if
you are planning for the future,
planning to beat inflation over the long
term,
then then you need to be you need to
have, you know, you need to own assets
and hold some cash by all means for for
that time, you know, for that
generational entry point. But, you know,
investing is about taking the rough with
the smooth, I think. You you never you
never buy the bottom in the same way
that you you never sell the top. So,
it's really about being, you know,
what is it? Time in the market rather
than timing the market. If you're not in
it, you ain't going to win it.
>> Very well said. If you're not in it, you
ain't going to win it. Ben, same
question for you. Is this the time to
sit out? Just kind of like let it kind
of uh you know, percolate, then come
back in or just say, "You know what?
Maybe a little bit here, a little bit
there."
>> I mean, with regards to crypto, the time
to sit out was like, you know, 8 months
ago. And I mean, now I feel like as I
think the right strategy for crypto is
just ignore it, you know, for like the
end of the midterm year until about July
and then start looking for deals.
And
you know, I mean, that that worked in
2018. It worked in 2022.
Yeah. Maybe it'll work again in 2026.
So, No, I mean, I I think having some
cash makes sense. Uh but you obviously
don't ever want to be 100% cash without
the ability to deploy anything cuz then
you just
you know, the purchasing power of the
dollar is going asymptotically to zero.
So,
I mean Guy what Guy said is correct. Um
>> Mhm.
>> So, yeah. I mean I I I think you have to
you have to own assets over the long
term otherwise inflation will eat you
alive. You just have to you have to own
the right assets, right? So, that's the
thing a lot of people make a mistake is
a mistake a lot of people make is that
they buy the wrong things. They buy like
you know, garbage stuff and then assume
it's going to make them rich and and
then it goes to zero. So, as long as
you're buying the right things, then
um
then that's the way I think to to
outperform inflation especially if you
if you buy like market like you know,
total market stuff like that, then it it
takes a lot less energy and that market
generally trends up with time and then
you don't have to stock pick if you
don't want to. Um but yeah, I mean I
think that
you have to own assets over the long
long term and normally the end of
mid-term years offer pretty good pretty
good entry points uh sort of ride out
for the next cycle.
>> Exactly. Well said. You know what? Just
to just to tie that up, it's let's be
honest. If we don't own assets and like
you guys both said, inflation is going
to eat us alive, but also it's boring.
Can you imagine how boring it is just to
sit on mountains and mountains of cash
and not do anything and not get to wake
up and take a look at your portfolio and
go, "Wow, it's up 30 40%." Or on the
flip side go, "Wow, it's down 30 or
40%." I know people will say that sounds
kind of crazy, but that's why we're in
crypto and digital assets and that's
just pretty much how it is.
So, speaking of that and doing risk,
here is my new play. I didn't tell
uh Guy and Ben this, but uh
I like to gamble sometimes. And I think
that it's good to go out not good
but I think this bet I'm going to make
is going to be pretty well great
as far as with uh Kolachi and
Polymarket. And here's the bet that I am
making and it's going to be huge.
So,
the question is over on Polymarket is
will the guy or guy from CoinBureau
attend the ITC conference in Miami on
November 20th to 22nd. Now, look, I'm
not going to sit here and say that I
don't have insider information.
But, I will just say this that over time
it was a pretty low probability. Right
now, we're at 50/50. So, the question
that has to come through is
will this actually happen? If you don't
know what I'm talking about, there is a
conference coming up in Miami
November 20th to 22nd. And I got to tell
you, if you are a family man or family
woman and you want to just take a little
bit of a break, come out there for
three, four, five days or something like
that. Visit Miami. It's going to be in
November and the rest of the United
States is going to be cold as hell. So,
why don't you come in and do the little
conference? We're going to have uh well,
I'll be there for sure.
Uh Ben will be there, David Lin, Garrett
Soloway, even Aldo, and uh Epic
Economist, oh, the Crypto Kid.
And uh you get to see the actual team.
It's going to be a good time. And then
also, for you 28% of people who just
watch their TV, there is a QR code you
can scan here to go to the actual
website. Or, if you're on your mobile
phone or desktop device, take a look in
the uh description and you can find the
link there. So, the question, of course,
comes down to will Guy make it to Miami?
Guy, I don't want to give you any any
insider track, but uh what's your
feeling on this one for Polymarket?
>> Ooh. Well, it's uh it's it's something
we're
it's something we're talking about, but
I couldn't I couldn't possibly confirm
either way. You know, Dubai, Miami,
that's a that's a long old trip.
Um but uh we are we we're considering
it, that's for sure.
>> That's why you got to come. You you come
through Puerto Rico.
You stay at a at a at a reasonable place
that uh maybe some of us could provide
at a reasonable discount and then you
could you come over to Florida. So
anyway.
>> Okay.
Okay.
>> And then and then before we get to Q&A,
Ben, anything you want to talk about the
as far as as far as the conference, what
do we got going on for there?
>> We're still adding speakers. Like we're
we're like we we reset a lot of people
are like talking about that stuff. By
the way, this is my first conference
like throwing my first conference, so
um you know,
it's sort of a learning experience uh
but I think it'll be a lot of fun. We'll
probably have one of our normal uh ITC
parties, which I think Rob's been to a
few of those. So, should be a good time.
>> Should be a good time. Well, everybody,
that will conclude it for today's show.
Like today's video, thumbs up,
subscribe, don't forget to
to uh subscribe to these two gentlemen's
channel even though they don't really
need much more subscribers. Guy with his
2.7 million and Ben
Congratulations passing the the 1
million mark. I forgot to say that in
the show.
>> Ah. Oh, now I'm almost almost a third of
what what or no, I guess a little more
than a third of what what Guy has.
>> [laughter]
>> Not too bad, not too bad.
>> I'll tell you the secret to it, Ben, is
is get all those subscribers in 2021
when crypto is
>> Ah, that was my mistake. That was my
mistake.
>> You just need to build that time
machine, go back in time
>> if my thumbnail game had been better
than better back [laughter] then, maybe.
>> Hey, that that thumbnail's that
thumbnail game is getting strong, I will
tell you. Let's see. The Raven Ice has
come on, Guy, kick back and get a vodka
cran in Miami and uh yeah, if you guys
come to the event, I will buy you
a drink.
Now, if it's a thousand if it's a
thousand people, it's going to be
Keystone Light, but if it's just a
couple hundred.
>> How how we not talked about the World
Cup is is is a good question.
>> That would be a good one. That'd be a
good one for you guys too to talk about.
Yes.
>> I mean
I Guy, I'm just going to say like I mean
England they didn't have a great game
the other day. I don't know if you saw
it.
>> No. I I didn't see it because again it
was on as an ungodly hour where I am and
I'm glad I didn't because a nil-nil draw
against Ghana is no one's idea of a good
time.
Um but I'm I'm reliably informed that
we're saving it for the bigger games.
So
>> Yeah.
>> Um it was very sad to see Scotland go
out though. Well, I don't I do I don't
think technically Scotland are out. I
think by I think there's a chance that
they could still squeeze through but
it's not looking it's not looking great.
They they lost three-nil to Brazil which
wasn't exactly surprising seeing as
Brazil are pretty good.
>> I don't think this will make you feel
any better but Ghana Ghana beat the
United States in the World Cup in 2006
and 2010.
>> Oh, no.
>> and then we got our revenge in I think
2014 maybe but not that that would make
you feel any better just cuz
or I mean [laughter]
Yeah, the US but look I don't know. I
I'm I'm a perusable right now on the on
the on the US soccer team. Let's go.
>> Okay. I I mean I I'm just I'm just so
amazed Ben by how how much you've gotten
into the World Cup.
>> Yeah, I've always been into soccer. Like
soccer soccer was the main sport I
played growing up. Uh
Like I
I played soccer, basketball, and
baseball but soccer was the one I liked
most. And
yeah, like I've always been into it. I
think the the reason why this time is
different
is because there's just nothing else
going on in the market. So what else am
I going to talk about?
>> USA dominance.
Brazil
>> Yeah, and it also adds a lot I think
that the World Cup is in the States, you
know? Like it it makes it even more
exciting. Like I got to go to one of the
USA games a few weeks ago, like one of
the warm-up matches. So, like it makes
it even more exciting. Also, there is a
couple of couple World Cups ago, the USA
didn't make it, I don't think.
>> Yeah.
>> Um
to What was it the World Cup or the
Olympics? I I think it was the Yeah, the
World Cup. They didn't even make it to
the World Cup. Um
you know,
at some point in the last decade. So,
>> Yeah.
>> I'm not as into it when they're not
there. But I mean, listen, last World
Cup, I will say the the finals,
Argentina and France, that was one of
the best games I've ever seen. Like one
of the most exciting games.
>> That was a good That was a great game,
yeah. That was a great game. The The US,
I think yeah, the US uh are very sort of
hit and miss. But I mean, the US women's
team
uh one of the best in the world, I
think.
>> Yeah. Guy, I also I have a bone to pick
with Guy, actually.
This
>> [laughter]
>> This This has come up a lot. And And I'm
going to I'm going to ask you, why does
everyone from the UK give Americans such
a hard time for calling it soccer when
the when the term soccer originated from
the UK?
>> Because
because for for whatever reason, the
term soccer is is no longer is no longer
used in the UK. Like you would do We We
We call it football because it's you
know, it you kick the ball with your
foot.
Um
>> [laughter]
>> Have you guys seen the uh the SNL skit
where they're like they're they're
they're talking about like George
Washington going to the New World and
stuff and and he's like, "We're going to
play football." And he's like, "It's a
It's a sport where you throw a ball with
your hands."
>> [laughter]
>> And then And then he's like, and they're
like, "Wait, so there's no kicking?" And
he's like, "There's a little kicking."
>> I've seen that sketch cuz you told me
about it, Ben. You told me when you were
over here in Dubai. I think you sent me
the link.
>> It is really funny.
>> Yeah. So, everyone should watch it if
they haven't seen it.
>> Yeah, that is a good one. Yeah, yeah,
yeah.
Hey, here's some questions real quick
and then we'll get to get going out of
here. Let's see.
What time on the registration day should
we show up at the Marriott? Just
everybody to make this simple, if you go
to that website they actually have some
recommendations for where to actually
stay.
Marriott Marquis Miami Kimpton Epic
Hotel InterContinental Miami. I am
looking for the Hotel sticks
but it's not listed here.
>> I think the uh the first thing is at
5:00 p.m. I believe. We're going to be
like welcome drinks, that kind of stuff
at the hotel on
uh Friday and then the conference is
Saturday. Uh the main conference and
we're going to we're going to fill in
some more stuff on Friday and Sunday, I
believe. We just haven't figured out
exactly what. Um
but I I believe 5:00 and I'll I'll let
you guys know if that
changes, but as of right now I think
5:00 is
um
cuz we want we want to give people time
to actually like check into the hotel.
You know, on Friday and usually you
can't check in until what like 3:00 or
4:00?
>> Yeah, that's Well, that's why we start
drinking.
Anyhow, it's up to you guys.
And somebody says Rich Comm says Guy
must come. Hey, I'm you know, I'm just
putting it out there. This is what Poly
Market is is is doing.
>> have NFA Live live.
>> That's crazy. Let's not go Let's not go
overboard.
>> Does Does anyone know that Rob me and
Guy, we've never been in the same place
at the same time in the real world.
>> It's all done with mirrors.
>> I've met Rob and I've met Guy and I
think Rob has met Guy, but we've never
actually seen each other all all at the
same time.
>> That's right.
Let's see.
>> One day. One day. Maybe maybe soon.
>> Hey, one day or or maybe just the uh
Coin Bureau team, whichever whichever
comes actually after it. Hey, how about
this question? Any chance of Lynn or Bob
as speakers?
>> So, we've reached out. We're we're still
working on that. Um
uh
some a lot of people are are just trying
to figure out if they can if they can
make it work at that point, you know,
like in in November. Um but we're going
to be adding more speakers. Like I don't
know for sure exactly. I think um
we have a few more likely coming um that
we haven't added yet. Like I think uh
I think maybe Jason Pizzino is
interested in in speaking.
>> He talks a lot more about like real
estate. We're trying I mean the
conference is more than just crypto, you
know, I mean it is and um
I mean it kind of goes along with what
Rob said earlier, right? There's always
a bull market somewhere. And um
so yeah, we'll we'll have we'll reach
out to as many people and try to get
those people there. And and by the way,
I mean the the goal is for it to be
different than
you know,
other like crypto conferences and stuff.
It It's not just
it's not just going to be like treasury
companies
Yeah.
Talk after talk after talk.
>> Sounds a lot more fun. How about this
one?
Uh Van Life says, "Hey, I'm betting my
money on quantum computing stocks for
the next boom like AI." I don't really
am familiar with this. I know that the
uh government US government just get it
gave a push to quantum computing to give
their agencies only a timeline to I
think 2031 or 2028. So, any thoughts on
this one? I don't I'm not following this
or tracking this for the uh investments.
>> We've been We've been looking looking
into it a bit. I mean, you know, some of
the most some of the most sort of fairly
obvious like IBM, I think a big into
Google or obviously quantum.
Um but
yeah, I it it's um I so so often you
just sort of consider it in terms of
what it'll do to Bitcoin and indeed
everything else, but
yeah, it does it will be a thing at some
point. [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I think so. And uh it's coming
sooner than later. And then lastly,
let's let's finish up with some soccer
talk. Uh
someone says, "Ben isn't American." I'm
guessing that's because he's talked so
much about soccer. Look, people some
people like soccer. Some people enjoy
watching.
>> You know, I will say this because
think about it. Like, the US has what? 3
to 400 million people in it?
>> Sure.
>> Okay.
>> Give or take.
>> Most people care about basketball,
baseball, and American football, right?
Football.
Um, I'm just calling it American
football for the benefit of our
international uh host right here from,
you know, guy.
>> [laughter]
>> But,
if even if only 10% of the
if only 10% of the people in the United
States cared about soccer, that's still
like 30 to 40 million people, which is
probably around the same audience size
as a lot of the European countries uh
that that care about soccer. It's just
that in the United States, there's just
an astronomically more larger number of
people that care about, you know, uh
other sports, so that it seems like it
just seems like soccer isn't popular at
all. Um, but it is popular. Like, I
mean, I've been to soccer games and
they're a lot of times I actually went
to um
the
the uh the national championship game in
soccer uh this past year. So, I mean, I
it was actually it's more popular than
people think. It just pales in
comparison to like, you know, the NBA or
the NFL.
>> Yeah.
>> I think well, I mean, cuz I I remember
reading a while back that one of the
reasons football was becoming more
popular in in the US
you know, football as in
>> I didn't realize I didn't realize
American football was becoming it was
already really popular.
>> [laughter]
>> Proper football, I should say, was
becoming more popular in the US because,
you know, there were a lot of there was
a lot of immigration from
from Latin America. And obviously,
football culture there is a lot more
ingrained. So, you know,
a a larger proportion of the US
population sort of comes from a football
culture cuz I think kind of, you know,
that's what you
that's what you need in a way in order
to sort of get popularity. It needs to
be sort of quite strongly a part of the
culture. And in the UK, for instance, it
is. It's like a sort of cultural
cornerstone, really.
But, yeah, as you say, Ben, it's there's
so much competition. Like, when you
think of
when you think of American sports, you
think of of baseball, basketball, and
and whatever American football is.
Um
So, you know, but when you think of when
you think of British sports, you know,
football and football is near the top.
So, it's about getting that I think
maybe, you know, as in a few more
generations, it will be, you know, it'll
keep getting more and more popular
because that football culture will
build.
>> All right, I feel like you're going to
soon start telling us we should be using
the metric system, you know.
Easy. Let's not go too far.
>> [laughter]
>> One day. That's
I'm not going to die on that hill today.
>> Yeah. All right, everybody. This is
we're going a little bit late. Again, I
want to thank Ben and Guy for coming on.
Links are in the description for
anything we just talked about today. And
next week we are with Guy on Coin Bureau
channel, so we'll set check you guys out
for Thursday. That's it for today. Thank
you, gentlemen. I appreciate you, and
I'll see everybody on the next one.
>> Adios.